Guide to the Thomas S. Foley Photographs 1905-1995
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Family and Political Photographs
  - Negatives, City of Spokane, Washington, undated (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Foley's Cat, undated (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Foley's Dog, Alice, undated (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - On Wilderness Trip to Cascade Mountains with Heather Foley, undated (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Passport Photos, undated (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Signed Black and White, undated (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Heather Foley - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Various Congressional Representatives, circa 1970-1993 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Various Social Events, circa 1986-1994 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, circa 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Miscellaneous Unfiled Solo Shots, circa 1975-1994 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Unknown Groups and Individuals, circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Unknown Groups and Individuals, 1970-1994 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Luncheons with Unidentifed Groups, circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Foley with unknown groups and individuals circa 1980's, circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Foley with unknown groups and individuals 1990's, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Unknown Groups and Individuals, undated (Box 6, Folder 109)
- Campaign Photographs and Related Material
  - Deputy Prosecutor of Spokane, Washington, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Portraits, 1960s (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Color Portrait, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Old Campaign - Folder 1, 1960s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Old Campaign - Folder 2, 1960s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Studio Portraits, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Close-Up Mats with Printing Plates, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - On Capitol Steps with Heather Foley, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Candid Shots with Heather Foley, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Election Night, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Election Night, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Campaign, 1978 August (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Billboards, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 5 x 7 Color, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Leisure with Heather Foley, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Close-Ups, Smiling, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Slides of Campaign Photographs, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Close-Ups, Animated, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Campaign, circa late 1970s (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Campaign, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Campaign, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Close-Up Negatives, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Campaign, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Slides of Campaign Photographs, 1986 September (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Campaign, circa 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Contact Prints, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Campaign, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Campaign, 1987 March 31 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Campaign Slides, 1987 September (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Dukakis-Bentsen Event in Washington State, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 5 x 7 Glosses, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Speaker Portrait, circa 1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Campaign - Folder 1, circa 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Campaign - Folder 2, circa 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Campaign - Folder 3, circa 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Campaign - Folder 4, circa 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Black and White Campaign Prints, circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - "Good Recent Close-Ups", 1991 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Campaign, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Campaign Portraits, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Campaign with Heather Foley, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Campaign Slides with Heather Foley, 1992 October (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Life" Magazine, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- International Photographs
  - President of Argentina, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - President of Armenia, 1992 April (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - President of Armania, 1992 August (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Prime Minister of Australia, Robert Hawke, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Prime Minister of Australia, Robert Hawke, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Prime Minister of Australia, Robert Hawke, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Chancellor of Austria, 1983 February (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - President of Austria's Federal Economic Chamber of Parliament, Leopold Maderthaner, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - President of Austria, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Prime Minister of Bangladesh, Sheikh Mujibur Rahman, circa 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Prime Minister of Belgium, 1982 February (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Brazilian Delegation, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - President of Brazil, Jose Sarney, 1986 September (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Queen Elizabeth II of the United Kingdom, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - London Trip with Speaker Tip O'Neill, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Great Britain Bipartisan Parliamentary Group, Speaker Tip O'Neill, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Queen Elizabeth II of the United Kingdom and Prince Phillip in Seattle, Washington, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - British-American Parliamentary Exchange in Bermuda, 1986 April (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Speaker of the United Kingdom House of Commons, Betty Boothroyd, in the U.S., circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Prime Minister of the United Kingdom, John Major, in the U.S., 1990 December (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Prime Minister of the United Kingdom, Margaret Thatcher, at Congressional Address, 1985 March (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Queen Elizabeth II of the United Kingdom in the U.S., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Former Prime Minister of the United Kingdom, Margaret Thatcher, in the U.S., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - British-American Parliamentary Group 50th Anniversary, in London, 1991 June 29-1991 July 7 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - British-American Parliamentary Group, 1991 July (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Prime Minister of the United Kingdom, John Major, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Embassy of the United Kingdom in Washington, D.C., 1994 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Convocation Speech at Bishops University, Quebec, Canada, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Prime Minister of Canada, Brian Mulroney, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Prime Minister of Canada, Brian Mulroney, in U.S., 1989 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Prime Minister of Canada, Brian Mulroney, at the Canadian Embassy in the U.S. (signed), 1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Premier of the People's Republic of China, Zhao Ziayang, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Vice President Walter Mondale Trip to China, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - President of Columbia, Virgilio Barco Vargas, in the U.S., circa 1988 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - President of Cyprus, George Vassiliou, 1991 June (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - President of Czechoslovakia, Vaclav Havel, in the U.S., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - U.S. Ambassador to Denmark, John Langeloth Loeb Jr., with President Ronald Reagan (signed), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Queen Margrethe II of Denmark, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - In Egypt, circa 1976 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Arab-American Council for Cultural and Economic Exchange, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - President of Egypt, Anwar Sadat, 1981 Spring (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Greeting the President of Egypt, Hosni Mubarak, with Jim Wright, 1982 January (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - President of Egypt, Hosni Mubarak, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - President of Egypt, Hosni Mubarak, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - European Parliament in the U.S., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - President of the European Commission, Jacques Delors, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - President of Finland, Mauno Koivisto, 1991 June (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Former Foreign Minister of France at Foreign Affairs Tea, 1981 March (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - President of France, Francois Mitterrand, at Joint Session of Congress, 1984 March (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Attache of the Ministry for Food, Agriculture and Forests of Germany, Steinhoff, Mayor Lueder, Berlin and Hans, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Foreign Minister of Germany at Foreign Affairs Tea, 1981 March (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - President of Germany, 1983 October (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Chancellor of Germany, Helmut Kohl, 1988 February (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Minister of Foreign Affairs of Germany, Hans-Dietrich Genscher, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Chancellor of Germany, Helmut Kohl, in the U.S., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - "Prime Minister" of Germany, circa 1992 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - President of Germany, Richard Von Weizsaker at Joint Meeting, 1992 April (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Chancellor of Germany, Helmut Kohl, in the U.S., 1993 May (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Ecumenical Patriarch of Constantinople, Demetrios I, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Ecumenical Patriarch of Constantinople, Demetrios I, and Paul Tsongas, circa 1989 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Ecumenical Patriarch of Constantinople, Demetrios I, in the U.S., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Prime Minister of Greece, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Greek Independence Day Celebration, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Grenada, circa 1985 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - President of Guatamala, Jorge Serrano Elias, in the U.S., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Prime Minister of Hungary, Jozsef Antall, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - President of Haiti, Jean-Bertrand Aristide, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - President of Haiti, Jean-Bertrand Aristide, and President Bill Clinton, circa 1993 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Prime Minister of India, Indira Gandhi, 1982 July (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Prime Minister of India, Rajiv Gandhi, 1985 Spring (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Prime Minister of India, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Shah of Iran, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - U.S. Ambassador to Ireland, William V. Shannon, at Sachs Hotel, in Dublin, 1979 April (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Irish Ambassador to the U.S., Sean Donlon, and Secretary of State Alexander Haig, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Foreign Minister of Ireland at "Friends of Ireland" Meeting, 1981 October (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Irish Ambassador to the U.S., Sean Donlon, and Jim Wright, in the U.S., 1981 October (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Prime Minister of Ireland, Charles Haughey, and Tip O'Neill at Party, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - "Friends of Ireland" Trip, 1982 June (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Prime Minister of Ireland, Garret FitzGerald, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Irish Ambassador to the U.S., Padraig MacKernan, and Jim Wright in the U.S., 1988 March (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Ambassador of Ireland and Margaret Heckler, circa 1989 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Prime Minister of Ireland, Charles Haughey, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - In Ireland, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - House Leandership visit to Ireland, 1971 August 31- 1971 September 7 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - President of Ireland, Mary Robinson, in Ireland, 1991 September (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Leader of Sinn Fein, Gerry Adams, 1994 October (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - House Leadership Visit to Ireland, 1991 August 31-1991 September 07 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - President of Ireland, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Prime Minister of Israel, Menachem Begin, Tip O'Neal at Congressional Treaty Reception, circa 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Prime Minister of Israel, Menachem Begin, 1980 March (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - President of Israel, Chaim Herzog, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ambassador to Israel, circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Prime Minister of Israel, Yitzhak Shamir, 1990 December (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Prime Minister of Israel, Yitzhak Rabin, circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - President of Italy, Sandro Pertini, 1982 March 25 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - At Italian Delegation in the U.S., 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Prime Minister of Italy, Giulio Andreotti, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Prime Minister of Italy, circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Address of the President of Italy, Francesco Cossiga, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Japanese Food Agency Team, 1974 May (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - U.S.-Japan Parliamentary Exchange, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Japanese Socialist Party visit to the U.S., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - "Wheatgrowers Reception for Japanese", 1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Prime Minister of Japan, Takeo Miki, 1976 December (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Japan Representative and Foreign Affairs Committee at Breakfast, circa 1979 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - U.S.-Japan Parliamentary Exchange at Prime Minister's Home, 1980 January 14 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Prime Minister of Japan, 1980 May (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - U.S.-Japan Parliamentary Exchange, circa 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Prime Minister of Japan, Zenko Suzuki at U.S.-Japan Parliamentary Exchange, 1982 January (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Japan Food Agency Team, 1982 August (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Visit of Prime Minister of Japan, Yasuhiro Nakasone, 1983 January (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - 98th Congress, 1st Session Visit to Japan, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - At Speakers Luncheon for Prime Minister of Japan, Yasuhiro Nakasone, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Prime Minister of Japan, Yasuhiro Nakasone, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Shimoda Conference, 1987 May 15 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Shimoda Conference - Japan, 1987 May (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Prime Minister of Japan, Noboru Takeshita, 1988 January 13 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Trip to Japan, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - U.S.-Japan Parliamentary Exchange, 1988 April (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Japanese House Representative, Kabun Muto, in U.S., 1988 May (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Ambassador of Japan, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - International Monetary and Economic Research Institute, Japan, 1989 June 12 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Japanese Food Agency Team, 1991 Fall (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Hiroshima Peace Memorial Service, 1991 December (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - King Hussein of Jordan, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - King Hussein of Jordan, 1993 June (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - King Hussein of Jordan, 1994 June (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - King Hussein of Jordan and Prime Minister of Israel, Yitzhak Rabin in the U.S., 1994 September (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - House Special Delegation Trip to Korea, 1969 February (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Korean National Assembly with Heather Foley, Speaker Carl Albert, Delegates and Wives, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - South Korean Ambassador to the U.S., Pyong-Choon Hahm, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Majority Leaders with Korean Officials, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - President of South Korea, Chun Doo-Hwan, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Speaker of the National Assembly of South Korea and Sergeant at Arms, Ben Guthrie, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - President of South Korea, Roh Tae-Woo, 1989 October (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - President of South Korea, Roh Tae-Woo, 1993 November (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - President of Liberia, Samuel Doe and Representative Clement Zablocki at Foreign Affairs Committee, circa 1982 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Leadership with President of Mexico, Miguel De La Madrid Hurtado, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Greeting the King of Morocco, 1982 May (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Queen Beatrix of the Netherlands, 1982 April (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Norwegian Ambassador to the U.S., Knut Hedemann, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Queen Sonja of Norway, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Prime Minister of Norway, 1994 May (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Prime Minister of Pakistan, Benazir Bhutto, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Chairman of the Palestine Liberation Organization, Yasser Arafat, undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - President of the Phillipines, Corazon Aquino, 1986 September (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - President of the Phillipines, Corazon Aquino, 1989 November (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - President of the Phillipines, Fidel Ramos, 1993 November (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - President of Poland, Lech Walesa, circa 1985 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - President of Poland, Lech Walesa, 1989 November (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - President of Poland, Lech Walesa, 1991 March (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Prime Minister of Portugal, Francisco Pinto Balsemao, 1982 December (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - U.S. Ambassador to Rome Maxwell M. Rabb, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - General Secretary of the Soviet Union, Leonid Brezhnez, and Soviet Delegation, circa 1975 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Soviet Delegation, 1979 November (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Trip to the Soviet Union, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - First Secretary of Ukraine, Volodymyr Shcherbytsky, and Soviet Delegation, 1985 March 3-1985 March 13 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Trip to the Soviet Union, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Soviet Students, circa 1988 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Defense Committee of the Supreme Soviet, circa 1988 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Soviet Delegation, 1991 June (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - President of Russia, Boris Yeltsin, 1991 July (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Alexy II, Patriarch of Moscow and all Russia, 1991 November 14 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Mikhail Gorbachev visit to the U.S., circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - President of Russia, Boris Yeltsin's, World Tour/Visit to the U.S., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - President of Russia, Boris Yeltsin, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Governor of Eastern Province of Saudi Arabia, Muhammad Bin Fahd Al Saud, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Visit to Saudi Arabia (Gulf War) with President George H. W. Bush, 1990 November (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Prime Minister of Singapore, Lee Kuan Yew, circa 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - President of South Africa, Frederik Willem de Klerk, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Nelson Mandela at Joint Meeting of Congress, 1990 June (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - President of South Africa, Nelson Mandela, visit to the U.S., 1994 October (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - President of Spain, Felipe Gonzalez, 1983 June (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Speaker of the Legislature of Sweden, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Thai Delegation, 1990 June (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "Taiwan Trek", 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - President of Ukraine, Leonid Kravchuk, 1992 May (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - War Tour of Vietnam, circa 1967 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - In Yugoslavia on Tour of Eastern Europe with Speaker Carl Albert, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified International Groups and Individuals, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Large Material
  - Personalized Album of the Inaguration of President Bill Clinton and Vice President Al Gore, circa 1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Campaign Contact Sheets, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - President-Elect Bill Clinton and Senator Al Gore, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Representatives Wright and Cohelo, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Representatives Wright, Gephardt, O'Neal, Michelle, Lott, Keap, circa 1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hillary Clinton at Joint Sessions of Congress, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Various Constituents, Signed and Matted, circa 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Adress to Congress with President George H. W. Bush and Vice President Dan Quayle, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Queen Elizabeth II of the United Kingdom, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Being Sworn In, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)